# **Brice Reilly**

## Senior Full Stack Developer

Canada | 2136165183 | goldenstar007.dev@gmail.com

Summary

Brice is a Senior Full Stack Developer with 10 years of experience creating web apps.

He has extensive knowledge of front-end JavaScript and browser APIs as well as significant experience with popular frameworks and libraries such as **React, Angular, Vue.** 

His deep full-stack experience includes **Node.js**, **Express**, **MongoDB** as well as more traditional technologies like **C/C#**, .**NET framework** and .**NET Core**.

He is also familiar with version control systems such as **Git, Bitbucket**, and code deployment in Microsoft **Azure** and **Firebase** and so on.

**Skills** 

HTML/CSS, JavaScript

8 years

React, Redux

4 years

AngularJS/2+

- Curana

5 years

## **Professional Experience**

JavaScript Developer

Excellent WebWorld

- Created Singe Page Applications using modern JavaScript Frameworks such like React, Angular, Vue.
- Developed Backend system using Node.js and integrated with frontend. Developed admin dashboard using Chart libraries

Technologies: React.js, Angular, Vue.js, Node.js, Backbone.js, Express.js, MongoDB, HTML/CSS, D3.js, HighCharts.js, AmCharts.js, etc.

Vue

2018 - 2019

2013 - 2017

2017 - 2018

3 years

Node.JS

5 years

MongoDB

5 years

JavaScript Developer

. . .

Upwork

- Built a dashboard that will analyze and display government data.
- Created pixel perfect and responsive pages using HTML/CSS
- Developed React & Angular & Node Projects.

Technologies: React.is, Angular, Node, HTML/CSS, Azure, Firebase, Git, Express.is

Laravel

3 years

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

3 years

Full Stack Developer

Dolphin Web Solution Pvt. Ltd.

- Developed a web-based facility management application, which provides effective control over requests, complaints or reported issues, incidents, work orders, reservations, visitor registration, car fleet management.
- Provided additional development on a social network web interface.
- Developed the frontend of logic of a unique system to develop a cross-platform software solution with a client-server architecture.

Technologies: C/C#, .NET Framework, .NET Core, Azure, Firebase, Web Socket, AWS, Web services

Azure

2 years

3 years

Git, Bitbucket

### **MEAN Development**

I worked as a full stack developer and there were 8 devs on this team.

Overall, there are sub apps - for users, admin and api. I created pixel perfect pages from the designs on Invision using React. JS and implemented state management using Redux and API integration using Redux Saga. Also, I contributed to the back end development using Node.js, Mongoose, Express.js, Redis. Furthermore, I implemented integration with various third party services such as SurveyGizmo, ActiveCampaign, GTM, Cron Jobs, Cohesion DB, Neilson DMP, etc.

#### https://lift.co





Home page

**Product Detail Page** 

## Vue / Laravel

This is a universal planning tool with a web interface and mobile application. I created all parts of this service from scratch, including DevOps with automated CI/CD and docker images; backend on Laravel; frontend on VueJS; mobile application on Ionic 4 and Capacitor.



**Universal Planning Tool** 

# MEAN development

Web(Angular6)&Mobile(React Native) app with Node on the Back-end. I was involved on all stages of development as a Full-Stack(Angular 6+ .Net) developer.

The app allows to physically and digitally manage the complete operational process of a company to ensure that each step in the workflow is covered. Whether a company is a home health agency, private practice liaison or long-term acute care (LTAC) hospital Zurvus Solution will fully automate the workflow process internally, minimize human error, and increase productivity





**Schedular of Employees** 

Dashboard statistics

## **Education**

Udemy.com Online Course

Computer Science 2016-2017

University of Toronto

Computer Science 2007 - 2008

Master of Science (MS)

University of Toronto

Computer Science 2003 - 2006

Bachelor of Science (BS)